{"data":[{"question":"The concert should have started two hours ago. I don't know what could have caused the ___.","a":"delay","b":"detail","c":"demand","d":"discount","answer":"1","explain":"- Delay:  when something does not happen or start when it should do (the concert should have stared but it haven't started yet-> delay","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The prevalence of smog over the city is both a ___ to the citizens and a danger to their health.","a":"surprise","b":"pleasure","c":"nuisance","d":"noise","answer":"3","explain":"- Nuisance: a person, thing, or situation that annoys you or causes problem\n\n- Smog -> no sound (noice is not correct); nagative meaning (suprise and pleasure are incorrect)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The law makes no ___ between the rich and the poor.","a":"agreement","b":"difference","c":"sense","d":"connection","answer":"2","explain":"- Make no difference between: there's no change ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Most scientists retain a special ___ for the first discovery or theory they produce in their own field.","a":"impression","b":"fault","c":"sign","d":"affection","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Affection: a feeling of liking or love and caring \n- This sentence mentions special feeling of scientist for their first achievement","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"In Japan today a fierce ___ is going on about primary schools between traditionalists and progressives.","a":"contest","b":"debate","c":"fighting","d":"battle","answer":"2","explain":"- Contest: discussion of a particular subject that often continues for a long time and in which people express different opinion","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The United States was founded on the ___ that all men are created equal. Even in colonial New England, and, later, on the Western frontier, class lines were by no means as rigid as in Europe.","a":"distinction","b":"permission","c":"philosophy","d":"principle","answer":"4","explain":"- On the principle:  the basic idea that a plan or system is based on","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"He was poor, given to drinking, and always in debt. He would have been totally forgotten, had he not gone mad. But his madness released ___ that was in him. He was born again. A fountain of song rose up from the depth of his spirit.","a":"a hidden poet","b":"the hidden poet","c":"hidden poets","d":"the hidden poets","answer":"2","explain":"- The: used before singular and plural nouns when the noun is specific or particular\n\n+ In this case, \"hidden poet\" was determined by \"that was in him\"-> use definite article","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Whether ___ is an Englishman, a Frenchman, or a German is a matter of no real importance. His discoveries are open to all, and nothing but intelligence is required in order to profit by them.","a":"a man of science","b":"a man of the science","c":"the man of the science","d":"a man of a science","answer":"1","explain":"- A\/an: is used to refer to a non-specific or non-particular member of the group","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The famous painter Picasso was having some friends to lunch in his house in the south of France- One of them looked around and said, \" I notice you don't have any ___ on your walls. Why is that? Don't you like them? \" \"On the contrary, \" Picasso replied, \" It is just that I can't afford them\"","a":"Picasso","b":"member of the Picassos","c":"Picassos","d":"one of Picasso","answer":"3","explain":"\n-Picassos: Picasso's painting","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Mother went to the doctor for ___ about her stomach trouble.","a":"advice","b":"an advice","c":"the advice","d":"advices","answer":"1","explain":"- We usually use no article to talk about things in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}